Memory Game backend flow
trend query every 12 hours (0 - 11, 12 - 23)
wordnet script filters results (optional)
LLM judges each trend, rephrases them to be searchable nouns
criterea:
- proper nouns capitalized
- is a noun
- is not sexual, gorey, a curse word, 
each word/phrase gets an image in an index in these steps:
1) google image search api
2) google scraping
3) wikipedia fallback
if possible, I do not want clip art, images with white backgrounds, or AI images
the index is then available to download by clients